Chandra Prakash

Yoga Instructor/Coach

□ rcias2022@gmail.com

• Laxmi Nagar,Delhi

https://www.youtube.com/watch? v=QZOygkutUWo 7302473460

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chandra-prakash-963a6523b

Chandra 98872121



About Me

Experienced and passionate, with a love for educating, instructing & coaching today's youth in all aspects of yoga. Withover 3 years of experience & advance training in national & international Yoga competitions. Adept in creating a comprehensive and well-rounded curriculum that meets educational requirements and standards. Able to act as a facilitator of powerful learning experiences, while allowing students to dictate certain lessons and lead with curiosity. Familiar with many renowned yogic philosophies, aimed at supporting a child academically, physically, emotionally, socially & spiritually. Forth dedication, skill and the desire to positively impact the lives of children.

Skills

Communication	• • • •	Critical thinking	•••	Time Management	• • • •
Leadership	•••	Computer Proficiency	••••	Subject Matter Experts	• • • •
Teaching and powdagogy	• • • •				

Work Experience	
DSVV, Yoga Instructor	Jan 2019 - Mar 2020 Haridwar
Villagers, Yoga Teacher	Jul 2020 - Jan 2021 Dulhin Bazar, Patna
District Administration, Yogic Psychologist	Jan 2021 - Aug 2021 Patna
New B.D.Public School, Yoga Teacher	Aug 2021 - Dec 2021 Patna
Kendriya Vidyalaya, Yoga Coach	Mar 2022 - Mar 2023 Khagaul,Patna
Kendriya Vidyalaya, Yoga Teacher	Apr 2023 - Present Goale Market, Delhi

Projects

Data Observer & Analyst, Malnutrition in School Going Childrens

Awareness Program Manager for overlapping benifits of Nutrition & Yoga.

Education

B.D.Public School, Matriculation, All Subjects

Mar 2014 - Mar 2015 Hajipur, Vaishali, Bihar.

Jul 2015 - Feb 2017 PATNA

Dev Sanskriti Vishwavidyalay, Bachelor of Yogic Science (HONOURS)

Jul 2017 - Jul 2020 Haridwar, Uttarakhand, India

Dev Sanskriti Vishwavidyalaya, Master's of Arts in History & Indian Culture

Aug 2020 - May 2022 Haridwar

• • • •

Certification

3rd World Yoga Festival & Championship, Organised by World Real Yoga Alliance, Under auspices of International Yoga Federation, Hosted by Chandigarh University

The Grand Master of Yoga-2019, Namo Gange Trust

Blood Donation, Himalayan Hospital

Workshop on Fitness & Nutration, Dev Sanskriti Vishwavidyalay in association with Physical Education Foundation of India (PEFI)

HOLISTIC MENTAL HEALTH EDUCATION, Center for Scientific Spirituality Studies (DSVV)

TAI JI TRAINING, Jointly conducted by Yunnan Minzu University (YMU) AND DEV SANSKRITI VISHWAVIDYALAYA (DSVV).

DDDD DDD DDDDDD (DDDDD), INSTITUTE OF CONSCIOUSNESS FOR DIVINE EXCELLENCE IN SOCIETY, PRAGAYA KUNJ.

Yoga Teacher in NCC Camp CATC/10., 31 UK BATTALION NCC, HARIDWAR, UTTARAKHAND.

BHARATIYA SANSKRITI GYAN PARIKSHA, UNDER THE AEGIS OF-GAYATRI-TEERTH, HARIDWAR.

Inter-University Yoga Championship 2019-20, Association of Indian Universities

Inter-University Yoga Championship 2021-22, Association of Indian Universities

Achievements

Recently successfully completed "Sattipatthana" after doing three ten days courses. Selected as "Yoga Instructor for Yoga Workshop" organised by, Delhi Sanskrit Academy, Govt. of NCT Delhi. Represented University two times at Inter University Yoga Championship in 2020 & 2022 (As Team Captain).

Hobbies

Meditation & Yoga, T'ai Chi(Shadowboxing),Reading, Language Learning, Running, Gardening, Volunteering & Community Involvement.

Languages

 ● ● ● Lithuanian